Yeah. Hey Keem, welcome to Indie.
Uh, so you are you're far from the first
Lou Anorumo former player to to join the
Colts here. What is it about him that
keeps leading you guys back to him and
ultimately what led to you coming to
Indie?
>> Uh, man, I built up a great relationship
with uh Lou
time Cincinnati.
So, I mean, he's
I have a relationship, a good
relationship with him. I trust him. I
trust the system. I trust and his
ability to call a good defense. And um
so, I mean, it made it easy to
want to be here and play on uh his play
calling. Um and then, um just the
organization
on his own is has great history. um hear
a lot of great things about the
organization from former players and
caring players. So, I mean it was a
no-brainer
>> James
>> Hakee, welcome to Indianapolis. Um what
did you think you gained from that year
with the Cardinals and starting as many
games as you did?
Uh I think it's how you uh able to start
um I guess majority of the season. U
you uh gain a lot of experience. Uh you
gain a lot of experience where whether
it's good or bad go through the ups and
downs of the season. Uh, so you're able
to learn, you able to learn from, I
guess like a different perspective
other than
watching film and things like that.
You're actually in the on the field week
to week
u the preparation it takes to prepare
your body, prepare your mind for each
game, each week, each practice.
Uh so I mean you really learn like
like a different part of the the game
from a
a a starter point of view.
>> Joel, go ahead.
>> Ake did you play did you play the the
mic for Lou in Cincinnati and what was
your role like with him?
uh in Cincinnati. Um I would come in as
the third linebacker
in Cincinnati and um play like that
little niche spot and him been able to
like move me around wherever and um but
whether Pratt or Logan would have went
down. So I mean I was interchangeable at
playing. So I played
probably like seven seven or eight games
at Mike and I think five or six at will
when those guys went down
>> James
>> Ken from what I understand the the Colts
linebacker room is it's pretty open as
far as roles and and who could be out
there. So what have they told you about
the opportunity you might have here to
start to play or whatever have you?
Uh, I mean, I guess you said it said it
right there that the the room is wide
open. So, I mean, that's one of the
reasons why I'm here to to compete to,
uh, start and, uh, be on the field. So,
uh, I haven't really done much talking
with with them about that list. Uh, I'm
just here to come earn earn my spot on
this team and
and and do it that way.